The ocean covers over 70% of the surface of our planet, though, according to the National Ocean Service, 95% of it remains unexplored.
海洋覆盖了地球表面70%以上的区域，但据美国国家海洋和大气管理局称，其中95%的海域仍未被人类探索。
This is because under the surface is a dark and hostile environment with unrelenting high pressure, freezing temperatures and bizarre creatures in the depths.
这是因为海面之下是一个黑暗而恶劣的环境，有着持续的高压、严寒的温度，还有生活在深海里的奇异生物。
The Census of Marine Life reports more than 17,000 species living in the deep sea.
海洋生物普查报告显示，深海中生活着超过17000个物种。
The Greenland shark can live in depths of 7,200 feet and is a rarely seen Arctic predator said to live to 400 years old and reach 23 feet in length.
格陵兰睡鲨可以栖息在7200英尺的深海，这种罕见的北极捕食者据说能活到400岁，体长可达23英尺。
In order to battle the icy depths, Greenland sharks have chemicals in their skin which prevent ice crystals from forming on their body.
为了抵御深海的严寒，格陵兰睡鲨的皮肤中含有特殊化学物质，能防止冰晶在身体表面形成。
Another deep-sea creature is the giant squid, an animal that remains a mystery to scientists despite being the largest invertebrate on Earth.
另一种深海生物是大王乌贼，它是地球上体型最大的无脊椎动物，但对科学家来说，它至今仍是一个谜。
Living far below the surface, what we know has largely come from carcasses being washed ashore.
大王乌贼生活在海洋深处，我们对它的了解大多来自被冲上岸的尸体。
Marine biologists have found that they feed on fish, squid and possibly even small whales.
海洋生物学家发现，它们以鱼类、乌贼甚至小型鲸鱼为食。
They find prey using eyes which are ten inches wide, roughly the size of a dinner plate!
它们依靠直径达10英寸的眼睛寻找猎物，那尺寸差不多相当于一个餐盘！
Other unusual creatures include the vampire squid, which lives 2000 to 3000 feet under the ocean and is so-called because of its dark cloak that connects its eight arms.
其他奇特的生物还包括吸血鬼乌贼，它们生活在2000到3000英尺的深海，得名于连接着八条腕足的深色“斗篷”状皮肤。
There is also the dumbo octopus, named due to its resemblance to the elephant from the 1943 Disney film Dumbo, with its protruding ears.
还有小飞象章鱼，它的名字源于1943年迪士尼动画电影《小飞象》里的大象，因为它长着一对突出的“耳朵”。
Another unique creature is the anglerfish known for the light that hangs from its head.
另外一种独特的生物是琵琶鱼，它因头部悬挂着一个发光器官而闻名。
So, enjoy swimming, but don’t venture too far down – you never know what is lurking beneath!
所以，尽情享受游泳的乐趣吧，但不要冒险潜得太深——你永远不知道海底深处潜伏着什么生物！